emediaworld.com 2009-05-08

# eMediaWorld.com Privacy - eMediaWorld - Newswire Service - FreePressRelease

The following discloses our Privacy Policy... 

**What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?  
** Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any Web site within the eMediaWorld, Inc. Network, our Web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.

 **What are cookies?  
** From time to time, eMediaWorld, Inc. or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system and are thus widely used throughout the internet by millions of businesses. We use cookies to identify which areas of eMediaWorld, Inc. Network of Web sites you have visited, used or customized, so the next time you visit, those pages may be readily accessible. Our advertisers may also use cookies to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers and we may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our web sites. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site and other web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.

 **What other information do you request?  
** We may also request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a survey or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to e-mail newsletters, announcement lists, account updates or information about new products and services). Whenever we request the identity of a visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent.

In addition, eMediaWorld, Inc. will not send you email that you have not agreed to receive. We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new eMediaWorld, Inc. products and services. In many cases while ordering services you may be required to provide your postal or billing address. This information is never shared or given to outside third parties. It is only used in order to communicate with you directly about your account or other happenings at eMediaWorld, Inc. or their holdings. When you sign up for a eMediaWorld, Inc. forum, your name or alias is recorded solely for purposes of maintaining your own account within the forums. This information is not used to monitor your activity within a forum, nor is it used to identify you outside the eMediaWorld, Inc. Network in any way. When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.

 **What information do you collect when I purchase something?  
** If you are purchasing something from an eMediaWorld, Inc. property, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. This information may also be used by us to notify you of related product and services. Credit card and e-mail information will not be shared or sold to third parties for any purpose without your express permission.

Certain eMediaWorld, Inc. properties use a shopping cart feature that safeguards this information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted servers. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server, rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to intercept the information. Other eMediaWorld, Inc. media properties do not use SSL and thereby do not offer a secure coded way to transfer information.

In many instances when eMediaWorld, Inc. collects personal information, a reasonable effort is made to included a link to this Privacy Policy if applicable. Additionally, our privacy policy link is always available from our main web site at: http://www.eMediaWorld.com

Will you disclose the information you collect to outside third parties?  
eMediaWorld, Inc. will disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:

1) Conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on eMediaWorld, Inc. ,  
2) Protect and defend the rights or property of the eMediaWorld, Inc. Network of sites, or visitors to the eMediaWorld, Inc. Network of sites,  
3) Identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties,  
4) Cooperate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.  
eMediaWorld, Inc. uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. eMediaWorld, Inc. reserves the right to transfer information in connection with the sale of all or part of eMediaWorld, Inc. 's capital stock or assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. eMediaWorld, Inc. also links to a wide variety of other sites and contains advertisements of third parties. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users

 **Opt-in announcement List Privacy Policy  
** As an added benefit to the visitors of the eMediaWorld, Inc. Network of sites, we use our own Listkingpro Software to send e-mail announcements to individuals who request to receive them. When you sign up for a eMediaWorld, Inc. e-mail newsletter or email forum, you may be given the opportunity to also receive additional announcement lists from ListkingPro. Whether you want to receive these announcement lists is your choice; you should only receive those lists you affirmatively choose to.

 **What else should I know about my privacy when online?  
** The eMediaWorld, Inc. Network of web sites contains many links to other web sites. eMediaWorld, Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. eMediaWorld, Inc. does not share any of the individual personal information you provide to eMediaWorld, Inc. with any of the sites to which eMediaWorld, Inc. links, although eMediaWorld, Inc. may share aggregate data with such web sites (such as how many people use our web site etc.).

 **Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy.  
** Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example through e-mail, discussion lists, or elsewhere - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.  
Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. It is therefore wise to be careful and responsible whenever you're online.

 **Your Consent To This Agreement  
** By using our web site and network of web sites, you consent to the collection and use of information by eMediaWorld, Inc. as specified above. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Thank you for making eMediaWorld, Inc. one of the most popular and leading edge marketing and advertising companies on the internet today!
